Guide to the Daniel Cady Eaton Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1854-1895; Series I; 4' 9 1/2" (11 1/2 boxes)
  - Knapp, William Ireland, 1835-1908, 1884-1885, 1890, undated (Box 7, Folder 307)
  - Knieskern, Dr. Peter D., 1857-1859 (Box 7, Folder 308)
  - Knowlton, Frank Hall, 1860-, 1891 (Box 7, Folder 309)
  - Kuhn, Dr. Maximilian, 1868-1871 (Box 7, Folder 310)
  - Lake, Arthur C., 1889 (Box 7, Folder 311)
  - Laning, E., 1855-1856, 1858-1859 (Box 7, Folder 312)
  - Lapham, Increase Allen, 1811-1875, 1859, 1862, 1865 (Box 7, Folder 313)
  - Lauderdale, J. V., 1857 (Box 7, Folder 314)
  - Lawson, George, 1827-1895, 1863 (Box 7, Folder 315)
  - Lawson, George Newton, 1865-1929, 1893 (Box 7, Folder 316)
  - Leggett, William Henry, 1816-1882, 1868, 1873 (Box 7, Folder 317)
  - Leidy, Dr. Joseph, 1823-1891, 1874 (Box 7, Folder 318)
  - Leighton, Alton Winslow, 1857-1920, 1890 (Box 7, Folder 319)
  - Lemmon, John Gill, 1832-1908, 1877-1883, 1892, undated (Box 7, Folder 320)
  - Lemmon, Sara Allen (Plummer), 1876 (Box 7, Folder 321)
  - Lennebacker, Miss Helen, 1877, undated (Box 7, Folder 322)
  - Leonard, Emily Josephine, 1837-1884, 1883-1884 (Box 7, Folder 323)
  - Le Roy, Peter V., 1880 (Box 7, Folder 324)
  - Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889, 1866, 1868, 1874-1876, 1883-1884 (Box 7, Folder 325)
  - Lichtenthaler, G. W., 1880-1881 (Box 7, Folder 326)
  - Lisk, William H., 1881 (Box 7, Folder 327)
  - Little, Robbins, 1832-1912, 1878 (Box 7, Folder 328)
  - Livingston, Beverly, 1852-1883, 1874-1875, 1882 (Box 7, Folder 329)
  - Livingston, Francis A., 1883-1884 (Box 7, Folder 330)
  - Locke, Miss Ada Elsie, undated (Box 7, Folder 331)
  - Long, W. H. Jr., 1893-1894 (Box 7, Folder 332)
  - Lord, Mrs. Fanny C., 1880 (Box 7, Folder 333)
  - Loring, Charles Greely, Jr., d. 1902, 1858-1859 (Box 7, Folder 334)
  - Lowell, James R., 1885 (Box 7, Folder 335)
  - Lusk, Jennie C., 1874 (Box 7, Folder 336)
  - Lydgate, John M., 1876 (Box 7, Folder 337)
  - Lyon, William S., 1882, 1884 (Box 7, Folder 338)
  - Lyons, Curtis J., (1857?) (Box 7, Folder 339)
  - McCarthy, Gerald, 1891 (Box 7, Folder 340)
  - MacDougal, Daniel Trembly, 1865-, 1892 (Box 7, Folder 341)
  - Macfeely, Robert, 1826-1901, 1879 (Box 7, Folder 342)
  - McIntyre, M. H., 1876-1877 (Box 7, Folder 343)
  - MacMillan, Conway, 1867-, 1891, 1894 (Box 7, Folder 344)
  - Macoun, John, 1832-1920, 1872, 1876, 1880-1882, 1884, 1891-1894 (Box 7, Folder 345)
  - MacOwen, Peter (Dr.), 1830-1909, 1869, 1873 (Box 7, Folder 346)
  - Makino, Tomitaro, 1862-, 1886 (Box 7, Folder 347)
  - Mann, Horace, 1844-1868, 1863, 1865-1868 (Box 7, Folder 348)
  - Marsden, Samuel Arthur, 1854-1883, 1881-1882 (Box 7, Folder 349)
  - Martindale, Isaac Comly, 1842-1893, 1877 (Box 7, Folder 350)
  - Mason, Nathaniel Haslope, f1. 1855-1867, 1857 (Box 7, Folder 351)
  - Masters, Maxwell Tylden, 1833-1907, 1866 (Box 7, Folder 352)
  - Meehan, Thomas, 1826-, 1872 (Box 7, Folder 353)
  - Merriam, Clinton Hart, 1855-, 1883-1884, 1893 (Box 7, Folder 354)
  - Merriam, G. & C. & Company, 1890 (Box 7, Folder 355)
  - Merrill, J. Warren, 1874, 1877-1878 (Box 7, Folder 356)
  - Mertz, Henry N., 1878 (Box 7, Folder 357)
  - Metcalf, John Lee, 1881 (Box 7, Folder 358)
  - Metchersky, Princess, 1869 (Box 7, Folder 359)
  - Mettenius, Georg Heinrich, 1823-1866, 1859-1862 (Box 7, Folder 360)
  - Miller, Elihu Sanford, 1848-, 1871-1873 (Box 7, Folder 361)
  - Millington, Lucy A. (Mrs.), 1873-1874, 1880 (Box 7, Folder 362)
  - Minor, A. B., 1881 (Box 7, Folder 363)
  - Minor, William Chester, 1835-1920, 1859 (Box 7, Folder 364)
  - Mitsukuri, Kakichi, 1857-1909, 1886 (Box 8, Folder 365)
  - Mitten, William, 1819-1906, 1869, 1880, 1882 (Box 8, Folder 366)
  - Miyabe, Kingo, 1886 (Box 8, Folder 367)
  - Mohr, Charles Theodore, 1824-1901, 1868, 1877-1878, 1890, 1893, undated (Box 8, Folder 368)
  - Moore, Thomas, 1821-1887, 1857-1858 (Box 8, Folder 369)
  - Morgan, Andrew Price, 1881 (Box 8, Folder 370)
  - Morgan, Laura (Mrs.) V., 1874-1876 (Box 8, Folder 371)
  - Morong, Thomas, 1827-1894, 1880-1881 (Box 8, Folder 372)
  - Morris, Elizabeth C., 1859-1861 (Box 8, Folder 373)
  - Morris, Luzon Burritt, 1827-1895, 1890 (Box 8, Folder 374)
  - Morse, Eldridge, 1882 (Box 8, Folder 375)
  - Mueller, Ferdinand, freiherr von, 1825-1896, 1866, 1886-1887 (Box 8, Folder 376)
  - Murray, David, 1830-1905, 1881 (Box 8, Folder 377)
  - Myers, Frances J., 1878-1879, 1881 (Box 8, Folder 378)
  - Nadden, James A. & Co., 1877 (Box 8, Folder 379)
  - Nash, George Valentine, 1893 (Box 8, Folder 380)
  - Nason, Henry Bradford, 1831-1895, 1893 (Box 8, Folder 381)
  - The Nation, 1891 (Box 8, Folder 382)
  - Nevius, The Rev. Reuben Denton, 1827-, 1889 (Box 8, Folder 383)
  - New England Historic Genealogical Society, 1867 (Box 8, Folder 384)
  - New York Academy of Sciences, 1866 (Box 8, Folder 385)
  - Norton, Alice J., 1880-1881 (Box 8, Folder 386)
  - Norton, Edward, 1823-1894, 1858-1859 (Box 8, Folder 387)
  - Norton, Mary E. B., 1879-1880 (Box 8, Folder 388)
  - Norway, Royal University Senate, 1870 (Box 8, Folder 389)
  - Nowlin, Julia A., 1878 (Box 8, Folder 390)
  - Oliver, Daniel, 1830-1916, 1873-1874 (Box 8, Folder 391)
  - Olmstead, Lemuel Gregory, 1808-1882, 1874 (Box 8, Folder 392)
  - Olney, Stephen Thayer, 1812-1878, 1868, 1871-1873 (Box 8, Folder 393)
  - Orton, James, 1830-1877, 1869, 1873 (Box 8, Folder 394)
  - Owen, (Mrs.) Maria Louisa, 1880-1883, 1885-1886, 1888 (Box 8, Folder 395)
  - Packard, Alphous (?) Spring, Jr., 1839-1905, 1873 (Box 8, Folder 396)
  - Paine, John Alsop, Jr., 1840-1912, 1865 (Box 8, Folder 397)
  - Palmer, Edward, 1831-1911, 1870-1871, 1873, 1877, 1879, 1881, 1887-1888, undated (Box 8, Folder 398)
  - Palmer Slide Co., 1893 (Box 8, Folder 399)
  - Parish Bros., 1880 (Box 8, Folder 400)
  - Parish, Samuel Bonsall, 1838-, 1891 (Box 8, Folder 401)
  - Parker, Charles F., 1820-1883, 1875, 1878 (Box 8, Folder 402)
  - Parker, Mary Ann (Bissell) Coit, 1867-1869 (Box 8, Folder 403)
  - Parkinson, Richard [Heinrich Robert] 1844-1909?, 1874 (Box 8, Folder 404)
  - Parlatore, Filippo, 1816-1877, 1873 (Box 8, Folder 405)
  - Parry, Charles Christopher, 1823-1890, 1865, 1867-1877, 1879, 1883 (Box 8, Folder 406)
  - Parsons, Samuel Bowne, 1819-1906, 1876 (Box 8, Folder 407)
  - Patterson, Harry Norton, 1853-1919, 1878, 1880 (Box 8, Folder 408)
  - Payot, Venance, 1855-1856 (Box 8, Folder 409)
  - Peck, Charles Horton, 1833-1917, 1875, 1877, 1886, 1890-1891 (Box 8, Folder 410)
  - Peck, The Rev. David, 1825-1874, 1869, 1871-1872 (Box 8, Folder 411)
  - Pell, W. H., 1875 (Box 8, Folder 412)
  - Pelton, Miss Emily O., 1879 (Box 8, Folder 413)
  - Pennsylvania State College, 1891 (Box 8, Folder 414)
  - Perkins, George Henry, 1844-1933, 1888 (Box 8, Folder 415)
  - Peters, Thomas Minott, 1810-1888, 1874-1876, 1878 (Box 8, Folder 416)
  - Philadelphia Evening Bulletin, 1890 (Box 8, Folder 417)
  - Piper, Charles Vancouver, 1867-1926, 1889-1894 (Box 8, Folder 418)
  - Planchon, Prof. Julio Emilio, 1823-1888, 1872-1873 (Box 8, Folder 419)
  - Porter, Thomas Conrad, 1822-1901, 1856, 1863, 1868-1869, 1873, 1893 (Box 8, Folder 420)
  - Post, Alfred A., 1869 (Box 8, Folder 421)
  - Post, George Edward, 1838-1909, 1867-1869, 1871-1872 (Box 8, Folder 422)
  - Prang, L., & Co., 1878 (Box 8, Folder 423)
  - Prentiss, Albert Nelson, 1869 (Box 8, Folder 424)
  - Pringle, Cyrus Guernsey, 1838-1911, 1876-1880, 1890-1892 (Box 8, Folder 425)
  - Putnam, Granville B., 1872-1873 (Box 8, Folder 426)
  - Rand, Edward Lothrop, 1859-1924, 1891, 1894 (Box 8, Folder 427)
  - Rau, Eugene A., 1876, 1878 (Box 8, Folder 428)
  - Redfield, John Howard, 1815-1895, 1871, 1873, 1877-1880, 1883 (Box 9, Folder 429)
  - Reinsch, Paul, 1872 (Box 9, Folder 430)
  - Reynolds, L. M. (Mrs.), 1883 (Box 9, Folder 431)
  - Reynolds, Mary C. (Miss), 1877-1881, 1883-1884, 1886, 1888, 1892 (Box 9, Folder 432)
  - Richards, Robert Hallowell, 1844-1945, 1887 (Box 9, Folder 433)
  - Richardson, Dr. Tobias Gibson, 1827-1892, 1875, 1878 (Box 9, Folder 434)
  - Rickard, T., 1859 (Box 9, Folder 435)
  - Ricketts, Palmer Chamberlaine, 1856-, 1880, 1893 (Box 9, Folder 436)
  - Robbins, James Watson, 1801-1879, 1857, 1859, 1865-1867 (Box 9, Folder 437)
  - Robinson, Benjamin Lincoln, 1864-1935, 1894 (Box 9, Folder 438)
  - Robinson, J. O., 1873 (Box 9, Folder 439)
  - Robinson, John, 1846-1925, 1872-1874, 1876, undated (Box 9, Folder 440)
  - Roge, Charlotte (Mme.), 1885 (Box 9, Folder 441)
  - Rothrock, Joseph Trimble, 1839-, 1874-1877 (Box 9, Folder 442)
  - Roy, A. K., 1873 (Box 9, Folder 443)
  - Roy, Mrs. Jessie D., 1870-1875, 1877-1878 (Box 9, Folder 444)
  - Rusby, Henry Hurd, 1855-, 1880-1882 (Box 9, Folder 445)
  - Russell, Gurdon W., 1876 (Box 9, Folder 446)
  - Rust, Mary Olivia (Mrs. Stiles M.), 1875, 1879 (Box 9, Folder 447)
  - Safford, William Edwin, 1859-1926, 1888 (Box 9, Folder 448)
  - Salisbury, Edward Elbridge, 1814-1901, 1888 (Box 9, Folder 449)
  - Sampson, Mary C., 1891 (Box 9, Folder 450)
  - San Diego Society of Natural History, 1874 (Box 9, Folder 451)
  - Sands, J. C., 1892-1893 (Box 9, Folder 452)
  - Sanford, Lillie, 1881 (Box 9, Folder 453)
  - Santa Barbara, California, Society of Natural History, 1878 (Box 9, Folder 454)
  - Sargent, Charles Sprague, 1841-1927, 1873, 1881 (Box 9, Folder 455)
  - Sartwell, Henry Parker, 1792-1867, 1857-1859, 1864, 1866 (Box 9, Folder 456)
  - Sayre, Charles L. R., 1875-1876 (Box 9, Folder 457)
  - Scammon, F., 1859-1861, 1863 (Box 9, Folder 458)
  - Schimper, Wilhelm Philipp, 1808-1880, 1878 (Box 9, Folder 459)
  - Schneck, J., 1879, 1881, 1889 (Box 9, Folder 460)
  - Schott, Arthur Carl Victor, 1814-1875, 1859-1860, 1866-1868 (Box 9, Folder 461)
  - Schuyler, Eugene, 1840-1890, 1868-1869 (Box 9, Folder 462)
  - Scranton, Edward Sereno, 1840-, 1874 (Box 9, Folder 463)
  - Scudder, Samuel H., 1857 (Box 9, Folder 464)
  - Selden, George Baldwin, 1846-1922, 1879 (Box 9, Folder 465)
  - Setchell, William Albert, 1864-1943, 1882, 1885, 1888, 1890, 1893 (Box 9, Folder 466)
  - Seymour, Arthur Bliss, 1859-1933, 1892-1893 (Box 9, Folder 467)
  - Sheffield, Joseph Earl, 1793-1882, 1873 (Box 9, Folder 468)
  - Shepard, C. Antoinette, 1890 (Box 9, Folder 469)
  - Shepard, Edward Martin, 1854-1934, 1878 (Box 9, Folder 470)
  - Shepard, James, 1838-1926, 1889-1890 (Box 9, Folder 471)
  - Shinn, Charles Howard, 1852-1924, 1879 (Box 9, Folder 472)
  - Shockley, William H., 1878, 1886, 1888 (Box 9, Folder 473)
  - Short, Charles Wilkins, 1794-1863, 1858-1859 (Box 9, Folder 474)
  - Shurtleff, S., 1858, undated (Box 9, Folder 475)
  - Silliman, Benjamin, Jr., 1816-1885, 1858-1860, 1863, 1876, undated (Box 9, Folder 476)
  - Silliman, Susan Huldah (Forbes), 1819-1878, 1860, n.y. (Box 9, Folder 477)
  - Simons, Manley H., M.D., 1893-1894 (Box 9, Folder 478)
  - Small, Albert, d. 1898, 1878 (Box 9, Folder 479)
  - Small, John Kunkel, 1869-, 1890, 1893-1894 (Box 9, Folder 480)
  - Smith, Prof. Eugene Allen, 1841-1927, 1877, 1881 (Box 9, Folder 481)
  - Smith, Hamilton Lanphere, 1818-1903, 1870, 1872, 1874, 1876, 1880-1882 (Box 9, Folder 482)
  - Smith, John Donnell, 1829-1928, 1877-1884, 1886, 1888-1889, 1891, 1893 (Box 10, Folder 483)
  - Smith, Wilder, 1835-1891, 1889 (Box 10, Folder 484)
  - Smithsonian Institution, 1874, 1879 (Box 10, Folder 485)
  - Society of Alaskan Natural History & Ethnology, 1888 (Box 10, Folder 486)
  - Southwick, Francis B., 1881 (Box 10, Folder 487)
  - Spence, Mrs. E. Jane, 1877 (Box 10, Folder 488)
  - Spencer, Charles A., undated (Box 10, Folder 489)
  - Spruce, Richard, 1817-1893, 1893, undated (Box 10, Folder 490)
  - Stabler, George, 1839-1910, 1883 (Box 10, Folder 491)
  - Stanton, Elizabeth (Cady), 1815-1902, 1892 (Box 10, Folder 492)
  - Stark, Robert Mackenzie, 1815-1873, 1855 (Box 10, Folder 493)
  - Stechart & Wolff, 1873 (Box 10, Folder 494)
  - Stilwell, L. W., 1886-1887 (Box 10, Folder 495)
  - Stout, Richard, 1882 (Box 10, Folder 496)
  - Stout, William, d. 1882, 1878-1880 (Box 10, Folder 497)
  - Stratton, Thomas, 1881 (Box 10, Folder 498)
  - Stratton, William A. T., b. 1836, 1879 (Box 10, Folder 499)
  - Strong, Charles Hall, 1850-1914, 1874 (Box 10, Folder 500)
  - Sturm, J. W., 1861 (Box 10, Folder 501)
  - Sturtevant, Edmund D., 1890 (Box 10, Folder 502)
  - Sullivant, William Starling, 1803-1873, 1856, 1857 (Box 10, Folder 503)
  - Summers, Mrs. Lucia (Mrs. R. W. S.), 1874, 1877-1879, 1885 (Box 10, Folder 504)
  - Sutton & Co., 1893 (Box 10, Folder 505)
  - Sweetser, Henry Edward, 1847-1870, 1861 (Box 10, Folder 506)
  - Tatnall, Edward, 1874, 1886 (Box 10, Folder 507)
  - Taylor, John Ellor, 1837-1895, 1873 (Box 10, Folder 508)
  - Tenney, W. A., 1871-1872 (Box 10, Folder 509)
  - Thacher, Thomas Anthony, 1815-1886, 1863-1864, 1878 (Box 10, Folder 510)
  - Thaxter, Roland, 1858-1932, 1890-1891 (Box 10, Folder 511)
  - Thayer, H. C., 1888-1889 (Box 10, Folder 512)
  - Thomas, George Brinton, 1836-1920, 1890 (Box 10, Folder 513)
  - Thurber, George, 1821-1890, 1857-1860, 1868, n.y. (Box 10, Folder 514)
  - Thuret, Gustave Adolphe, 1817-1875, 1873 (Box 10, Folder 515)
  - Tillinghast, Frank N., 1887 (Box 10, Folder 516)
  - Todd, W. F., 1894 (Box 10, Folder 517)
  - Tompkins, W. R., 1876 (Box 10, Folder 518)
  - Torrey, John, 1796-1873 (includes photograph), 1856-1862, 1865, 1868-1871, undated (Box 10, Folder 519)
  - Townsend, Charles H. T., 1894 (Box 10, Folder 520)
  - Tracy, Mrs. Clarissa (Tucker), 1818-, 1882, 1889 (Box 10, Folder 521)
  - Tracy, Samuel Mills, 1847-1920, 1886, 1890 (Box 10, Folder 522)
  - Train, Abner L., 1887 (Box 10, Folder 523)
  - Treadwell, John H., 1872 (Box 10, Folder 524)
  - Trelease, William, 1857-1945, 1884, 1890, 1893-1894 (Box 10, Folder 525)
  - Trumbull, James Hammond, 1821-1897, 1889 (Box 10, Folder 526)
  - Tucker, George, 1835-1908, 1872 (Box 10, Folder 527)
  - Tuckerman, Edward, 1817-1886, 1858-1860, 1862, 1869-1870 (Box 10, Folder 528)
  - Underwood, Lucien Marcus, 1853-1907, 1877-1878, 1880, 1887, 1889-1890, 1892-1893 (Box 10, Folder 529)
  - U. S. Army Corps of Engineers. Wheeler, Lt. George M., 1876, 1878 (Box 10, Folder 530)
  - U. S. Bureau of Fisheries, 1894 (Box 10, Folder 531)
  - U. S. Dept. of Agriculture, Div. of Botany. Coville, Frederick V., 1892-1894 (Box 10, Folder 532)
  - United States Telephone Mfg. Co., 1881 (Box 10, Folder 533)
  - Van Siclen, George West, 1879 (Box 10, Folder 534)
  - Vasey, George, 1822-1893, 1858-1863, 1868-1869, 1872-1875, 1877, 1881-1882, 1886 (Box 10, Folder 535)
  - Vogdes, Lt. Anthony Wayne, 1843-, 1847 (Box 11, Folder 536)
  - Waghorne, The Rev. Arthur Charles, d. 1900, 1893-1894 (Box 11, Folder 537)
  - Waldo, Gerald, 1884 (Box 11, Folder 538)
  - Wale, George, 1875-1877 (Box 11, Folder 539)
  - Wall, George, 1821-1894, 1873-1874, 1882, 1884 (Box 11, Folder 540)
  - Ward, Richard Halstead, 1837-1917, 1857 (Box 11, Folder 541)
  - Warne, H. A., 1875 (Box 11, Folder 542)
  - Warnstorf, Carl, 1837-, 1892-1895 (Box 11, Folder 543)
  - Waters, Campbell Easter, 1872-, 1894 (Box 11, Folder 544)
  - Watson, Benjamin Marston, Jr., d. 1918, 1878 (Box 11, Folder 545)
  - Watson, Sereno, 1827-1892, 1869, 1871-1878 (Box 11, Folder 546)
  - Watson, Sereno, 1827-1892, 1879-1881, 1887-1891, undated (Box 11, Folder 547)
  - Watt, David A. Poe, 1864-1875, 1880, 1889, undated (Box 11, Folder 548)
  - Waycott, S. (Miss), 1889 (Box 11, Folder 549)
  - Webber, Herbert John, 1865-, 1893 (Box 11, Folder 550)
  - Weller, Charles Heald, 1870-1927, 1894 (Box 11, Folder 551)
  - Westerman, Bernard & Co., 1864, 1871-1872 (Box 11, Folder 552)
  - Wetnerby, A. G., 1882 (Box 11, Folder 553)
  - Wheatly, W., 1889 (Box 11, Folder 554)
  - Wheeler, Isabelle H. (Mrs.), 1889-1890 (Box 11, Folder 555)
  - Wheeler, John Davenport, 1834-1922, 1858, 1860-1864, 1872, undated (Box 11, Folder 556)
  - Wheeler, Theodosia Mary (Davenport), 1810-1883, 1861 (Box 11, Folder 557)
  - Whidden, Bradlee, 1892 (Box 11, Folder 558)
  - White, Andrew Dickson, 1832-1918, 1867, 1874 (Box 11, Folder 558A)
  - White, Henry, 1803-1880, 1871 (Box 11, Folder 559)
  - White, Moses Clark, 1819-1900, 1858 (Box 11, Folder 560)
  - Whitney, Eli, 1847-1924, 1870 (Box 11, Folder 561)
  - Whitney, William Dwight, 1827-1894, 1876 (Box 11, Folder 562)
  - Whittlesey, Heman Charles, 1857-1923, 1894 (Box 11, Folder 563)
  - Wibbe, J. Herman, 1877, 1880 (Box 11, Folder 564)
  - Wildberger, Robert H., 1878-1879 (Box 11, Folder 565)
  - Wilkeson, Samuel, 1817-1889, 1878 (Box 11, Folder 566)
  - Willard, Sarah H., undated (Box 11, Folder 567)
  - Willey, Henry, 1824-, 1867-1869, 1872, 1874-1876, 1880 (Box 11, Folder 568)
  - Williams, Henry T., 1873 (Box 11, Folder 569)
  - Williams, J. R., 1881 (Box 11, Folder 570)
  - Williams, John, 1817-1899, 1892 (Box 11, Folder 571)
  - Williams, Robert Stratham, 1859-1945, 1880, 1889 (Box 11, Folder 572)
  - Williamson, John, 1878-1879 (Box 11, Folder 573)
  - Wilson, James, 1882, 1893 (Box 11, Folder 574)
  - Wilson, Nathaniel, 1809-1874, 1867 (Box 11, Folder 575)
  - Wilson, William, 1799-1871, 1856 (Box 11, Folder 576)
  - Wolle, The Rev. Francis, 1817-1895, 1875, 1877 (Box 12, Folder 577)
  - Women's Auxiliary Conference, Boston, Mass., 1866 (Box 12, Folder 578)
  - Wood, Alphonso, 1810-1881, 1858, 1864, 1868 (Box 12, Folder 579)
  - Wood, William, 1869 (Box 12, Folder 580)
  - Woolsey, Theodore Dwight, 1801-1889, 1870, undated (Box 12, Folder 581)
  - Woolson, (Miss) Constance Fenimore 1840-1894, 1875 (Box 12, Folder 582)
  - Woolson, Geo. C., 1878 (Box 12, Folder 583)
  - Wright, Charles 1811-1885 and Wright, John G: (brothers), 1857-1863, 1865-1866, 1868-1869, 1871, 1878, 1881, 1883 (Box 12, Folder 584)
  - Wright, Helen S., 1878 (Box 12, Folder 585)
  - Wright, Dr. S. Hart, 1874, 1880 (Box 12, Folder 586)
  - Wright, William Greenwood, 1831-, 1879-1880 (Box 12, Folder 587)
  - Yates, Dr. Lorenzo Gordin, 1837-, 1878-1879, 1889 (Box 12, Folder 588)
  - Yoshinaga, Yoshisato, 1889 (Box 12, Folder 589)
  - Young, Andrew Harvey, 1875-1876, 1879 (Box 12, Folder 590)
  - Andersson, N.J. to Asa Gray (copy by Daniel Cady Eaton), undated (Box 12, Folder 591)
  - Baker, J. G. to Asa Gray (copy by Daniel Cady Eaton), 1874 (Box 12, Folder 592)
  - Booth, Mary Ann to Professor Silliman, 1874 (Box 12, Folder 593)
  - Fries, E. to Asa Gray (copy by Daniel Cady Eaton), 1858 (Box 12, Folder 594)
  - Lesquereux, Leo to Professor J. A. Allen, 1883 (Box 12, Folder 595)
  - Macoun, John to Mrs. E. G. Britton, 1891-1892, undated (Box 12, Folder 596)
  - Macoun, John to Mr. Evans, 1897 (Box 12, Folder 597)
  - Peck, Charles Horton to P. H. Dudley, 1886 (Box 12, Folder 598)
  - Sands, J. C. to Wesley R. Coe, 1892 (Box 12, Folder 599)
- Writings, 1860, 1863-1866, 1868, 1875-1880, 1896; Series II; 5" (1 box)
  This series is divided into two sections: "Writings" and "Writings of Others." The "Writings" section contains primarily plant lists and plant catalogs in Eaton's hand. Among the printed material is an address, a copy of a dissertation presented at Harvard in 1860 written in Latin, and a paper entitled "On the Genus Woodsia." The material is arranged alphabetically by category.
  The five items in the "Writings of Others" section are arranged alphabetically by title.
  - Writings
    - Address: "Talking About Botany. Its Bearings on Horticulture", 1880 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Book: The Ferns of North America Vol. II (fragment), 1880 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Dissertation: "Felices Wrightianae et Fendlerianae", December 1860 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - List of Miscellaneous Botanical Specimens, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Notes on Ferns and Algae, 1875-1880 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Notes on Ferns in some European Herbaria, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Paper: "On the Genus Woodsia" printed in the Canadian Naturalist, April 1865 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Plant Catalog (37 pages), undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Plant Catalog (44 pages), undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Plant Catalog comparing flora of various regions, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Plant list: California Ferns from Mr. W. H. Brewer, May 1863 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Plant lists from scientific journals: notes, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Plant lists: lichen, 1865, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - "Sphagna Boreali - Americana Exsiccata" by Eaton and Edwin Faxon, 1893, 1896 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Writings of Others
    - "Botanical Contributions" Asa Gray, November 1865 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - "Ferns from California, collected 1860-1862," William Henry Brewer, 1864 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - "Insectivorous Plants - Additional Investigations," Asa Gray, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - "Introduction. On the General Characters of Mosses." Leo Lesquereux, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - "On the Fertilization of Ferns" by Ed. Strasburger, 1868 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Special Files, 1859, 1862-1863, 1865, 1868, 1872, 1874-1888, 1890-1894, 1897; Series III; 5" (1 box)
  The Special Files contain genealogical material, including copies of materials from England concerning the Eaton family, a scrapbook of newspaper clippings about the Eatons in the United States, and material concerning the Eaton Family Association, as well as a copy of Daniel Cady Eaton's John Eaton of Dedham, Mass. The series also contains a mounted plant specimen and miscellaneous printed material on botany.
  - Genealogical Material
    - Births, deaths, early history of some Eatons in America, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Circular letters and Reunion Program, 1881-1882, 1885 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Eaton Family Association Report, 1888 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - John Eaton of Dedham, Mass. and some of His Descendants by Daniel Cady Eaton (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook of newspaper clippings relating to ancestry of Daniel Cady Eaton, 1859, 1865, 1868, 1877, 1881-1885, 1887-1888, 1890-1894. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Transcripts of legal records of the Eaton family in Great Britain, 1353, 1522-1524, 1543-1544, 1580, 1601-1602, 1604-1606, 1609, 1611, 1613, 1617-1618, 1624, 1630, 1637, 1639-1640, 1642, 1668, 1672 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Plant Specimen
    - Plant Specimen, 1893 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Printed Material
    - Article: "Insectivorous Plants I & II" appeared in The Nation, 1874 April 2, 9 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - "Check List of the Ferns of North America North of Mexico", 1873 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous pamphlets on botany, 1874, 1877-1878, 1882, 1886, 1890-1891 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Newspaper clippings on botanists, 1884, 1897 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Newspaper clippings on the dissemination of seeds, 1863, 1874-1875, 1879, 1883, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Newspaper clippings on weeds, 1862, 1872, 1875-1881, 1883 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Numbered Checklist of North American Plants, 1892 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Pamphlets and clippings on ferns, 1877, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Reprint: "Was it Hypnotism?", 1890 (Box 14, Folder 16)